somebody commented on
my video from yesterday and it reminded
me of this video
that i've been meaning to make for a
while which is
the division that is on the left that
does not exist on the right
by the very definition of how we split
the left and the right
the right is generally thought of as
a entity that wants things to remain the
same
or go back to the good old days they
might not agree on when those good old
days existed
so how far back we need to go but they
want to go back
there is one linear process to go back
on even if we
its history is a very gray area and we
don't necessarily know we think we know
so we'll go back to that time period or
we will remain the same
it's hard to keep society the same but
it's easy to envision it staying the
same
and as things change and you get used to
them they become
the current version of now and therefore
what you're fighting to keep
so as things change the right's not okay
with the change
stereotypically but once it happens we
all get acclimatized to it
and then they want that to remain the
same the left
by the by definition because they're
just divided
remain the same different there are
infinite ways to make our current
reality
different than it currently is going
backwards is a linear process going
forwards is like all of the possibility
tendrils reaching out into infinite
infinity
so you know even if you we could agree
that we want
universal healthcare what does universal
healthcare look like
because we don't currently have it in
the united states we have it in canada
we know what it looks like we don't want
it to go to what states is we would like
it even more universal
um on the left on the right they want to
go for it towards the states look at
that beautiful
beautiful option that they're
the very tools that are used on the left
don't work on the right the right can't
be cancelled
it can only kind of be cancelled with
actual truth
um and so people actually owning their
own self and being like
actually even though i was anti-gay my
whole life i am now gay
you can be canceled on the right but if
you're anti-gay pro-family values your
entire life and then are
as a male politician and that are found
with a male prostitute
you're good if you can apologize and say
that was a that was a problematic moment
despite the fact you cheated on your
wife despite the fact it was with
another man despite the fact it was the
man you paid for
that was illegal all of that's cool okay
and okay as long as you apologize
the left has the opposite where it's
like one bad thing you said from three
decades ago we're gonna dig that
puppy up and you're gonna be canceled
forever
so the left is cannibalizing itself
and the left also like we cancel and
we cancel differently the right buys
your and burns it which helps you
the left shows up at your speaking
engagements
yelling speaking louder than you which
just brings more attention and the best
publicity that they can find so the
right runners can find those people
it's like oh if the left isn't
protesting you we don't even want you
so i have less than two minutes left to
explain
what i think is the road forward
and it is that we can
disagree on why our current world is
broken
we just agree that it is broken because
to everyone whether you want it to
remain the same
or whether you want a beautiful future
it's
the agreement that it is broken knowing
we're not going to agree on why it's
broken
we can all have a beautiful future we
are living into
your beautiful future can even include
one that completely counteracts fine
only men and women are gonna get married
well how we're moving forward your
vision of the future is never gonna be
seen
um neither is my little gay queer utopia
probably so
so you're good on my i'm not having to
live my future and i'm good i'm
not having to live your future we can
disagree on what's broken in the
present we can disagree on our beautiful
utopian versions of the future
all we have to do is agree on one step
forward
ten thousand people can get together and
figure out how they live their little
heterosexual utopian life
and get to live that a little
incrementally forward cool it's not
going to expand to the rest of the world
it's just not because it's going
backwards
um my little queertopia also probably
won't expand the whole world because the
entire world's not queer
but having options you can have both of
those things simultaneously because
nobody with 10 000 people
has the power to inflict that on the
rest of the population just because they
think it's a better way
we don't have to agree on what's broken
we don't have to agree with the full
blueprint on the on the 5-10 year
25-year plan for
for humanity all we have to do is figure
out
how to agree on a 10 000 person project
how to create something that works for
those 10 000 people
and everyone's invited everyone can
create their project for their 10 000
people if your idea is so horrific you
can't bring on 10 000 people
yours doesn't get made a green on the
next step forward
is plausible we can agree on something
with 10 features and benefits
a lot more easily than we can agree on a
25 row
25 year roadmap that's going to change
things to infinite different directions
in pr in so doing that process we will
get to
a beautiful vision of the world that is
no single person's utopia
but is the combination of all of ours
which is the only way to get to
improvement anyway
if you maximize for one person's values
you get to dystopia
if you have individuals working for
their own value set
in understanding that other people have
other values
and we're all working towards our own
well understanding the tension of other
people working towards theirs
we can get to a beautiful beautiful
world
we're already there thanks